<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Edwin Sulaiman</title><link>https://edsulaiman.github.io/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Edwin Sulaiman</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 10:56:48 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://edsulaiman.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Moto1 Back Office</title><link>https://edsulaiman.github.io/projects/moto1-back-office/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 10:56:48 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://edsulaiman.github.io/projects/moto1-back-office/</guid><description>Moto1 Back Office is a comprehensive Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) application specially designed for the Moto1 workshop, empowering efficient management of employee, sales, marketing, finance, accounting, and inventory processes. This powerful app centralizes all aspects of workshop operations, ensuring seamless coordination and optimizing productivity.
Key Features:
Employee Management: Efficiently manage your workforce with Moto1 Back Office. From HR-related tasks such as attendance tracking, leave management, and performance evaluation to task assignments and scheduling, this app streamlines employee-related processes for increased efficiency.</description></item><item><title>Moto1 Pos</title><link>https://edsulaiman.github.io/projects/moto1-pos/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 10:49:30 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://edsulaiman.github.io/projects/moto1-pos/</guid><description>Moto1 POS is a dedicated Point of Sale (POS) application designed exclusively for the Moto1 workshop, streamlining the order management process with speed and precision. This user-friendly app is tailored to efficiently handle all your workshop&amp;rsquo;s order transactions, from quick service tasks to converting motorcycles to electric vehicles.
Key Features:
Efficient Order Reception: Moto1 POS simplifies the order reception process, allowing your workshop staff to swiftly capture customer requests. With a clean and intuitive interface, taking orders becomes seamless, minimizing wait times and enhancing customer satisfaction.</description></item><item><title>Moto1 Customer</title><link>https://edsulaiman.github.io/projects/moto1-customer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 10:47:26 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://edsulaiman.github.io/projects/moto1-customer/</guid><description>Moto1 Customer is a cutting-edge mobile application designed to revolutionize your motorcycle service and ownership experience. This customer-centric app is tailored exclusively for Moto1 workshop patrons, providing a seamless and personalized way to engage with the workshop and access a range of convenient services.
Key Features:
Effortless Service Booking: Booking motorcycle services has never been easier. With Moto1 Customer, you can quickly schedule appointments for routine maintenance, repairs, or electric motorcycle conversions at the touch of a button.</description></item><item><title>Hillsong Church</title><link>https://edsulaiman.github.io/projects/hillsong-church/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 17:27:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://edsulaiman.github.io/projects/hillsong-church/</guid><description>The Hillsong Church app is a powerful tool that brings people closer to their faith, providing a seamless and convenient way to connect with the church community. This app enables users to find and join the Hillsong Church, one of the most popular and dynamic churches in the world.
With the Hillsong Church app, users can send prayer requests or ask for help, connecting them with the broader community for support and guidance.</description></item><item><title>SIPOLI</title><link>https://edsulaiman.github.io/projects/sipoli/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 17:27:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://edsulaiman.github.io/projects/sipoli/</guid><description>The SIPOLI app is the official driving licence test app from the government, designed to make it easier and more convenient for people to prepare for their driving licence test. This app offers a wide range of features that make it easy for users to create new submissions, do psychotests, and view their test certificate, all from the convenience of their mobile device.</description></item></channel></rss>